<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Posts on </title>
    <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Posts on </description>
    <generator>Hugo 0.125.0</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 01 May 2024 12:39:42 +0530</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="http://localhost:1313/posts/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Exploring CI/CD Vulnerabilities in github actions</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/how-to-start-with-ci-cd-vulnerabilities/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 May 2024 12:39:42 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/how-to-start-with-ci-cd-vulnerabilities/</guid>
      <description>I hope this message finds you well. Today, I&amp;rsquo;m thrilled to share my journey and insights into exploring CI/CD vulnerabilities in GitHub Actions.&#xA;Getting started To start with actions It is crucial to understand the intricacies of action workflows and familiarize yourself with their functionality and the significance of each event. Crafting sample workflows can significantly aid comprehension.&#xA;To help you get started, I have a YouTube playlist with informative videos that will guide you in getting acquainted with action workflow</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>About</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 29 Apr 2024 01:07:28 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/about/</guid>
      <description>Introduction I am Anupam Singh, deeply interested in coding and hacking, with a primary focus on cybersecurity. My journey in these fields began during the lockdown period. I am particularly fascinated by application security, and I am always seeking to deepen my expertise through continuous research. In addition to my technical pursuits, I am an avid fan of anime, with a preference for action and psychological thrillers. I also enjoy exploring various aspects of history and space exploration, particularly the achievements of ancient civilizations and the future possibilities of space travel.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
